getlikefast.net 2015-07-17

# Privacy Policy - Get Like Fast

Please read these Terms of Service completely using getlikefast.net which is owned and operated by getlikefast.net Team. This Agreement documents the legally binding terms and conditions attached to the use of the Site at getlikefast.net. By using or accessing the Site in any way, viewing or browsing the Site, or adding your own content to the Site, you are agreeing to be bound by these Terms of Service. getlikefast.net is for education and experiment purpose only. We are not responsible in anyway of miss use of our service. In getlikefast.net user can share their htc access_token to our site by their own responsibility. getlikefast.net can use user token to perform Facebook likes/comment function on behalf of user by using their access_token. getlikefast.net is not responsible for using any other Facebook application token as getlikefast.net can accept Facebook application token by their user choice. getlikefast.net is only design and develop only for student or developer for better understanding of developing Facebook application. getlikefast.net perform only like/comment function on behalf of the user. We are not responsible that user are submitting their Facebook application token to our system and performing likes/comment function. If user want to know about developing code behind getlikefast.net he/she can get full information by paying us via several payment options. We does contain a number of links to other websites and online resources that are not owned or controlled by getlikefast.net developer or owner. getlikefast.net has no control over, and therefore cannot assume responsibility for, the content or general practices of any of these third party sites and/or services. Therefore, we strongly advise you to read the entire terms and conditions and privacy policy of any site that you visit as a result of following a link that is posted on our site. We reserves the right to modify these Terms of Service at any time. We do so by posting and drawing attention to the updated terms on the Site. Your decision to continue to visit and make use of the Site after such changes have been made constitutes your formal acceptance of the new Terms of Service. Therefore, we ask that you check and review this Agreement for such changes on an occasional basis. Should you not agree to any provision of this Agreement or any changes we make to this Agreement, we ask and advise that you do not use or continue to access getlikefast.net immediately.

## PRIVACY POLICY

This privacy policy sets out how getlikefast.net uses and protects any information that you give to getlikefast.net when you use this website.  
getlikefast.net is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.  
getlikefast.net may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from July 11, 2015.

## WHAT WE COLLECT?

We may collect the following information:  
Facebook Profile Id  
Facebook Access_Token

### WHAT WE DO WITH THE INFORMATION WE GATHER?

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:  
Internal record keeping.  
We may use the information to improve our products and services.  
We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.  
From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customize the website according to your interests.

### SECURITY

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

### HOW WE USE COOKIES

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.  
We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.  
Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.  
You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

### LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we can't be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide while visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

#### CONTROLLING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.  
You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please email support@getlikefast.net.  
If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
